Some people are afraid of all the wrong things.
A Walk Among the Tombstones is a crime, drama,
mystery film directed by Scott Frank.
Private investigator Matthew Scudder is hired by a drug kingpin
to find out who kidnapped and murdered his wife.
Matthew Scudder, played by Liam Neeson.
Kenny Kristo, played by Dan Stevens.
Ray, played by David Harbour.
Peter Kristo, played by Boyd Holbrook.
Jonas Loogan, played by Ólafur Darri Ólafsson.
TJ, played by Stro.
A Walk Among the Tombstones is a 2014 American neo-noir action thriller film directed and written
by Scott Frank, and based on the 1992 novel of the same name by Lawrence Block.
It stars Liam Neeson, Dan Stevens, David Harbour, and Boyd Holbrook.
The film was released on September 19, 2014.
The film received mostly positive reviews from critics and grossed $62 million
worldwide against a $28 million budget, making it a modest success.
Although Frank and Neeson hoped for further adaptations,
no more films have been made as of 2025.
The film explores themes of new york city, based on novel or
book, murder, private investigator, mafia.
The tone is intense and emotional and mind_bending.